http://nightmareonelmstreetfilms.com/site/about/privacy-policy

Press Kit
A Nightmare on Elm Street (2010)
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
Our website trackers collect information from you, such as screen
resolution, operating system, web browser and location. These statistics
are used by us when we make changes to website elements such as the
design, in order to optimize the site so that it looks great and
performs quickly for as many people as possible. To avoid abuse, your IP
is also stored for a short amount of time on the server.
We also collect information from you when you register on our site, forum, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey. When
registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked
to enter your name and/or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site
anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve this website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To process transactions
Your
information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged,
transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic e-mails
The e-mail address you provide for processing will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your user account.
Do we use cookies?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a website or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your
browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about
site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site
experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party
service providers to assist us in better understanding our site
visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us improve our website.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We
do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your
personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third
parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our
business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this
information confidential. We may also release your information when we
believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site
policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided
to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third-party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party
products or services on our website. These third-party sites have
separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no
responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these
linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site
and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because
we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in
compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We
therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside
parties without your consent.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We
are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online
Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone
under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all
directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
This policy was last modified on October 1, 2011
http://nightmareonelmstreetfilms.com
Recent News
A Nightmare on Elm Street SteelBook Blu-ray Coming in September
John Saxon Dies at 83
Exciting News: Like Freddy from the Ashes, the Nightmare on Elm Street Forum Lives Again!
Scream, Queen! My Nightmare on Elm Street Featured at Fringe! Queer Film Fest
Gibson Guitar Interviews Nightmare Composer Charles Bernstein in New Series
